Guide to the Stanford University, Queer Student Resources, Records SC0252
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2000-125
  - Subject Files
    - Gay and Lesbian issues dissertation articles (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Coming out articles (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gay Liberation Sculpture by G. Segal (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - GLAS Newsletters (1982- ) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Graduate women's network (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Heterosexuality at Stanford, misc. (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Heterosexuality Peninsula/South Bay, misc. (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Hewlett-Packard (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - High Tech Gays (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - High Tech Gays newsletter (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - High Tech Industry / Silicon Valley / Employment of Gays and Lesbians (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Hillel Stanford (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Homophobic Incidents, Stanford campus (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Hoover Institution (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Housing ads – anti-gay (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Human Biology 128 "Biosocial Aspects of Sexually Transmitted Diseases" (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Imperial AIDS Foundation (San Jose) (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Innovative Academic Courses (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Institute for Research on Women and Gender (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Institute of Lesbian Studies (Palo Alto) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Keplers (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - KBSU Radio (Stanford) (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Latino Community Issues - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Lively Arts at Stanford (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - "Living with AIDS" film (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - LOTS Gay B. Board (misc.) (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - LOTS Gay B. Board (Apr. 22, 1984 – Aug. 11, 1984) (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - LOTS Bboard Gay – Hard Copy (1985-86) (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - LOTS Gay B.Board (1985-87) (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - LOTS – B.Board Gay – Hard Copy (1985-87 continued) (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - LOTS Gay B.Board: discussion of George Segal's "Gay Liberation" defacement (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Maps and guides: Stanford campus (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Metropolitan Community Church – The Beacon - newsletter (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Memorial Church (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - The Men's Center (Palo Alto) (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Mid-Peninsula Rape Crisis Center (Palo Alto) (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Mid-Peninsula Support Network Newsletter (Mountain View, CA) (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Mobilization against AIDS – Peninsula South Bay Chapter (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Motion Picture Theater, Peninsula South Bay – misc. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Moxon/Lewis Gay and Lesbian Student Organizations Survey (1985-86) (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Music Department - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - NAMES Project San Francisco (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators – Network on Gay, Lesbian and Bisexual Concerns (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - National Gay Archives (NGA) Bulletin (LA) – continued by ILGA bulletin (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - National March on Washington Santa Clara County Organizing Committee (1987) (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - National Organization for Women Palo Alto Chapter (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - New Varsity Movie Palace and Restaurant, Palo Alto (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Non-Discrimination Policy - AIDS (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Non-Discrimination Policy - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - NOW Lesbian Rights Task Force (Palo Alto) (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - OASIS (Gays and Lesbians of Color Group) - Stanford (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Office of Graduate Studies (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Old Firehouse (1981 -) (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Okada House (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Our Paper San Jose (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Pacific Friends (S. F. and San Jose) (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Pacific Ventures (Mid-Peninsula and South Bay) (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Palo Alto High School (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Palo Alto Human Relations Commission (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Palo Alto Public Library (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Palo Alto Unified School District (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Palo Alto Weekly – misc. gay and lesbian stories (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Parents and Friends of Lesbians and Gays – mid-peninsula chapter (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Parents of Gays – Palo Alto chapter (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Parents and Friends of Gays of San Francisco and the Greater Bay Area Newsletter (S. F.) (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Party invitations – Peninsula/South Bay (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Peninsula/South Bay misc. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Peninsula Area Gay and Lesbian Community Council (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Peninsula Business and Professional Association (see also Peninsula Social Guild) (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Peninsula Business Guild (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Peninsula Gay and Lesbian Youth Group (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Peninsula Gay and Lesbian Youth Group – Awareness Program (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Peninsula No on 64 (1986) (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Peninsula Social Guild (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Peninsula Times Tribune (Palo Alto) – gay/lesbian news (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Personal Advertisements – Peninsula/South Bay – misc. publications (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Personal Advertisements – Peninsula/South Bay – The Advocate (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Personal Advertisements – Peninsula/South Bay – San Jose Metro (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Phone Sex Services – Peninsula/South Bay (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Planned Parenthood Association of San Mateo County (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Playboy (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - "Practical Joke" posters with gay content (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Printer's Inc. Bookstore (Palo Alto) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Psychology Department (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Queerland (Direct Action Group) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Rainbow Agenda (1987 - ) (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Rape Education Project (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Reasonable Doubt (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Recycle Books and Records (Palo Alto) (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Red Cross (Palo Alto) (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Residential Arts Program – Production of "Rent" (May 1986) (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Residential Arts Program – Production of "Moonlight Serenade" by Toni Press (Nov. 1986) (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Residential Education (office of) (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Revenue (Redwood City) (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Roble Hall (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Sadomasochism – misc. (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - San Francisco Bay Area Gay and Lesbian Historical Society (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - San Jose area – misc. (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - San Jose Metro – gay news (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - San Jose Mercury News, misc. stories, editorials, columns, letters (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - San Mateo County – misc. (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - San Mateo County – Dept. of Health Services (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - San Mateo County – Dept. of Health Services – AIDS Project (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - San Mateo County No on 64 Committee (1986) (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Santa Clara County – misc. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Santa Clara County Board of Supervisors – AIDS Community Task Force (1986-) (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Santa Clara County AIDS Foundation (San Jose) (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Santa Clara County Health Dept. (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Santa Clara University (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Scientists and Citizens against Prop 64 (Palo Alto) (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Sex Shops, Adult Bookstores – Peninsula/South Bay – misc. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Sexism – Stanford, misc. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Sexual Abuse of Children – Peninsula/South Bay – misc. (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Sexuality Discussion Group for Women (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Sexuality – Peninsula/South Bay – misc. (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Sexually Transmitted Diseases – Peninsula/South Bay (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Sha'ar Zahan, Congregation (Jewish) (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Signs: Journal of Women in Culture and Society (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Sister Spirit Women's Bookstore/Coffee House (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - "‘68" (feature film) (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - SLUG (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - South Bay Gay Parents (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - S2PARK – Students Speaking About Race and Culture, Stanford student group (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Stanford Democrats (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Stanford Federalist Society (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Alumni (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Business Students Association (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Counseling Group (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Law Students Association (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Medical Students Association (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Speakers Bureau (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Stanford Administrative Workshop materials (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Stanford Commemoration Committee (1988) (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Stanford AIDS Education Project (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Stanford Alumni Association (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Stanford Bookstore (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - "Stanford Cares" AIDS Benefit (10 May 1986) (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Stanford Child Custody Study (1985- ) (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Stanford College Republicans (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Stanford Women's Center (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Gertrude Stein Week (16-19 April 1985) (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - STARTS (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Stanford Graduate School of Business (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Stanford Help Center (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Stanford Humanities Center (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Stanford Interview (Fall 1982) Comparative Sex Survey (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Stanford/Ivy (Los Angeles Lesbian and Gay Alumni Club) (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Stanford LAG Club (see also S. U. Gay and Lesbian Alumni) (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Stanford Law School (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Stanford Gay and Lesbian Archives Project (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Stanford Magazine (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Stanford Daily Magazine (24 Jan. 1986) "Living a Different Love – Homosexuality at Stanford" (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Stanford Daily, misc. (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Stanford Daily, misc. features, reviews (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Stanford Daily, misc. editorials (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Stanford Daily, misc. news items (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Stanford Daily, misc. columns and letters (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Stanford Medical Center – general documentation (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Stanford Medical Center – AIDS research and treatment (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Stanford Medical Center Blood Bank (S. U. Blood Center) (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Stanford Museum - collections (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Stanford Organization for Lesbian and Gay Equality (SOLGE), 1987- (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Stanford Out of South Africa (SOSA) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Stanford Overseas Campuses (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Stanford Police Department (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Stanford Progressive Alliance (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Quad (Yearbook) (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Stanford Review (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Stanford Savoyards (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Student directory (1984-85) misc. typesetting – gay lesbian and women's sections (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Stanford Today (1987-88) (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association (see also Stanford LAG Club) (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stanford University Libraries – misc. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Stanford University Libraries – collections – AIDS materials (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Stanford University Libraries – collections – gay/lesbian studies gifts and book fund purchases (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Stanford University Press (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Stanford Women in Music Collection (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Straight Awareness Week (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford - misc. (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford - CA State University, North Ridge (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford - Caltech Lesbian and Gay Society (1985-) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford - Univ. of California, Berkeley – Graduate Gay and Lesbian Assembly (1981-82) (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford - UC Berkeley, GLU Newsletter (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford – UC Berkeley, Gay and Lesbian Union (1984-) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford – UC Los Angeles (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Student Groups non-Stanford – University of Washington, Seattle (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Gay Student Organizations – Non-Stanford, misc. (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - STOP – Students Opposed to Pornography (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Student organization services (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - SU-NET (Stanford Cable Television) Gay and Lesbian Programming (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - SWOPSI – misc. (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - SWOPSI 169 "Suppressed Perspectives" (Spring 1983) (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - SWOPSI 171 "Men in Difficulty Times" (Spring 1982) (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - SWOPSI 178 "Visions in Lesbian Literature" (Spring 1982) (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - SWOPSI 169 "Gay History/Gay Heritage" (Spring 1982) (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - SWOPSI 169 (Spring 1985) (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - SWOPSI 168 (Fall 1985) "Politics of Gender and Sexuality" (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - SWOPSI 168 (Fall 1986) (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Syntex (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - "Take Back the Night" March (8 April 1985) (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tearoom Activity – Stanford misc. documentation (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Times Tribune – features "AIDS: an Epidemic of Fear" series (Dec. 1985) (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Trellis Singles Magazine (Mountain View, CA) (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Trikon (Palo Alto) (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Tuesday films series (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Undergraduate English Association (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - United States Olympic Committee (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - University Lutheran Church / Stanford Lutheran Center (Palo Alto) (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - University of California Gay and Lesbian Alumni Association (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - The Vortex (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Wesley United Methodist Church (Palo Alto) (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Western Culture Program (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Western States Lesbian and Gay Students United (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Whiskey Gulch Neighborhood (East Palo Alto) (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Women and Children Together (San Carlos) (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Women Entertainment Forum (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Women's History Week (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - X-TV (Stanford cable) (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Jewish Groups
      - Ahavat Shalom (Newsletter of Congregation Ahavat Shalom, San Francisco, CA) (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - Haiyonah / The Dove (S.F.) (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Jewish Gaily Forward – Congregation Sha'ak Eahav Newsletter (San Francisco, CA) (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Jewish Gaily Forward (1985 -) (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - World Congress Digest – Newsletter of the World Congress of Gay and Lesbian Jewish Organizations (Evanston, IL) (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Lambda Institute
      - Teacher and Student Evaluations, Responses and Comments (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - Articles of Incorporation, By-Laws, Federal tax-exempt status, State Tax-exempt status, and Prospectus (Annual Report) Fiscal (1984-85) (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - Resource/referral list, reading list, additional program support info (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Mid-Peninsula Gay and Lesbian Youth Group
      - Resource and reading lists (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - Response letters to outreach (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - Blank forms/copies (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - Planning (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - People Files, Series 2
    - Stanford and Peninsula – misc. individuals (alphabetical) (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Misc. Stanford graduates (alphabetical) (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Misc. Stanford faculty and staff (alphabetical) (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Misc. GPU/GLAS members (not SU student, faculty or staff) (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Abrams, Donald (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Actenberg, Roberta (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Adam, Margie (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Adams, Joyce (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Aguirre, Valentin (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Alarcon, Francisco (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Albee, Edward (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Ambrogi, Thomas (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Andelson, Sheldon (Stanford BA 1952) (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Appel, Brent (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Aronson, Adam (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Bacigalupi, Rick (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - Baez, Joan (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Bao, Daniel (GLAS Steering Committee member) (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Barmeyer, Jeff (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Baxer, Ray (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - Bell, Derrick (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - Bellonson, Joel (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Bernfield, Merton, MD (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - Bernstein, Bobbi (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Berube, Allan (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Beyers, Charlotte (Stanford ‘71) (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Block, Steven Mark (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Bork, Robert H. (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Britt, Harry (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Britt, Richard (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Broder, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Broughton, James (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Brownmiller, Susan (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Burciaga, Jose Antonio (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Burger, Harold (Stanford Med. Center) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Calegari, Kevin (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Cameron, Kirk & Cameron, Paul (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Campbell, Tom (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Carey, Alice Ross (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Carnoy, Martin (Prof. Of Education and Economics) (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Carter, Jimmy (US President) (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Carter, Wendell (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Casselberry & Dupree (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Chang, Ann-Mei (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Christen, Pat (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Clark, Don (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Clever, Linda Hawes (Member, Board of Trustees) (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Clinton, Kate (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Cole, Jennifer (LGBCC Officer 88-89) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Sally (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Coles, Matt (gay rights lawyer) (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Collins, Jack (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Conklin, Diana (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Coors, Scott (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Cranston, Alan (US Senator; Stanford) (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Cuff, David (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Dague, Paul (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Cox, Allan (Dean of School of Earth Sciences) (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Daher, Douglas (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Dannemeyer, William (US Representative) (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Davidson, Ann & Julian (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Davis, Corey (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - DiFeliciantonio, Tina (MA Student/film) (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Doherty, Will (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Dorman, John (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Dover, Sir Kenneth (writing professor) (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Drury, Allen (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Dubbs, Julie (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Dunlap, Mary (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Dupont, Mark (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Dutton, Roz (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Eastman, Steve (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Edell, Michael (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Engelman, Edgar (MD) (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Evan, Derek (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Eyerly, Fred (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Fetterman, David M. (Asst. Prof Education) (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Fischer, Fritz (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Fitzpatrick, Toni (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Flounders, Bud (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Ford, David (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Forster, E. M. (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Friedman, Robert (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Gallagher (Comedian) (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Gallo, Dr. Robert (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Gans, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Gartrell, Nanette (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Gifford, April (Grad. Student – Russian) (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Goodstein, Edward (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Gorin, Ralph (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Grahn, Judy (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Greaves, Carlos (MD, counselor at CAPS) (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Ginsberg, Allen (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Gunn, Thom (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Gunther, Gerald (Prof., Law School) (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Gusterson, Hugh (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Gutierrez, Fernando (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Hanrahan, Noel (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Harrison, Lou (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Hart, Cary (CA State Senator) (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Harry Hay (Stanford alum) (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Henning, Tom (LGBCC officer) (Box 5, Folder 76)
    - Herrera, David (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Herriford, Wayne (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Herrington, Marvin (Chief, Stanford Police Dept.) (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Hiersch, Rhio (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Hinckley, Bennett (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Howton, Elizabeth (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Huerta, Mario (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Islas, Arturo (Prof. Of English) (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Johnson, Fenton (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Johnson, Sonia (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Jones, Cleve (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Kennedy, Anthony (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Kennedy, Donald (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Kizer, Kenneth (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Keeling, Dr. Richard (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Klepfisz, Irena (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Knapper, Karl (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Koskovich, Gerard (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Koop, c. Everett (US Surgeon General) (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Lisac, Andrew (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Loulan, Joanne (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Long, Toni (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Lewis, Richard (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - Lessing, Jill (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Leonard, Tom (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Leavitt, David (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Low, Sande (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Lyons, James (Dean of Student Affairs) (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - AIDS Education Project Records, Series 3
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - AIDS Research Archive (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - "Eroticizing Safe-Sex Workshop" 30 Jan. 1986, surveys (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - AIDS Education Project – Meyer Library exhibit (April 1986) (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - Fundraising – University Development Permissions (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Safe Sex Kit Handbooks (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - Final Report, 1985-86 academic year (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Stanford Cares – AIDS education packet (mailing to Deans of Students) May 1986 (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Peninsula/South Bay Resource Guide Draft (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - AIDS in the Workplace – misc. (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - Activism (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - Benefits and Fundraisers (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Business enterprises (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - California State Legislature (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - Blood Donation Issues (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - AIDS Education Project in the News (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Fiscal Year 1985-86 (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Fiscal Year 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Fiscal Year 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - AIDS benefit 1986-87 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - AIDS involvement network 1987-88 (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1985 - August (Box 5, Folder 126)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1985 - September (Box 5, Folder 127)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1985 - October (Box 5, Folder 128)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1985 - November (Box 5, Folder 129)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1985 - December (Box 5, Folder 130)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1986 - January (Box 5, Folder 131)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1986 - February (Box 5, Folder 132)
    - Clippings – Associated Press Wire 1986 - March (Box 5, Folder 133)
    - Clippings – editorials and letters to the editor (Box 5, Folder 134)
    - Clippings – feature stories, reviews, columns (Box 5, Folder 135)
    - Clippings – News Stories 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Clippings – News Stories 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Clippings – News Stories 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - News (1987) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Clips - 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Condom Information Materials (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Conferences and Symposia (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Ethnic minorities and AIDS (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Film and Video Productions (Box 6, Folder 9)